{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 87 + 20?",
      "answers": [
        "106",
        "107",
        "108"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "107",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 57 - 26?",
      "answers": [
        "29",
        "31",
        "32"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "31",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 1 * 8?",
      "answers": [
        "10",
        "8",
        "9"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 16 / 8?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "0"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 76 - 10?",
      "answers": [
        "66",
        "69",
        "65"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 99 / 11?",
      "answers": [
        "9",
        "12",
        "10"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5 * 3?",
      "answers": [
        "15",
        "14",
        "16"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 97 - 43?",
      "answers": [
        "55",
        "52",
        "54"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "54",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 99 - 26?",
      "answers": [
        "73",
        "75",
        "71"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "73",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 35 - 5?",
      "answers": [
        "32",
        "27",
        "30"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 110 / 10?",
      "answers": [
        "12",
        "9",
        "11"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 74 + 47?",
      "answers": [
        "121",
        "122",
        "123"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "121",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 53 - 9?",
      "answers": [
        "47",
        "44",
        "45"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 91 + 2?",
      "answers": [
        "93",
        "95",
        "94"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "93",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 97 - 74?",
      "answers": [
        "21",
        "23",
        "22"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 58 - 39?",
      "answers": [
        "17",
        "19",
        "18"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 30 + 98?",
      "answers": [
        "128",
        "131",
        "126"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "128",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 40 / 10?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 58 + 1?",
      "answers": [
        "56",
        "59",
        "57"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 88 - 29?",
      "answers": [
        "62",
        "59",
        "60"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 50 + 8?",
      "answers": [
        "58",
        "56",
        "61"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "58",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 84 / 7?",
      "answers": [
        "12",
        "10",
        "9"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 32 / 4?",
      "answers": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 76 + 26?",
      "answers": [
        "101",
        "100",
        "102"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "102",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 99 - 34?",
      "answers": [
        "65",
        "62",
        "64"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "65",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 98 - 81?",
      "answers": [
        "20",
        "17",
        "16"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9 * 1?",
      "answers": [
        "7",
        "9",
        "10"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 26 + 81?",
      "answers": [
        "106",
        "107",
        "104"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "107",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 70 / 7?",
      "answers": [
        "12",
        "10",
        "7"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 98 - 65?",
      "answers": [
        "30",
        "33",
        "36"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "33",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4 * 10?",
      "answers": [
        "39",
        "38",
        "40"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 85 - 29?",
      "answers": [
        "56",
        "57",
        "55"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 57 + 19?",
      "answers": [
        "79",
        "76",
        "75"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "76",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 * 3?",
      "answers": [
        "24",
        "21",
        "23"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 53 - 40?",
      "answers": [
        "13",
        "16",
        "12"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 14 + 35?",
      "answers": [
        "52",
        "49",
        "47"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 / 8?",
      "answers": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 * 12?",
      "answers": [
        "69",
        "70",
        "72"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "72",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4 * 5?",
      "answers": [
        "20",
        "17",
        "19"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 * 6?",
      "answers": [
        "18",
        "21",
        "20"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 - 6?",
      "answers": [
        "44",
        "45",
        "42"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "42",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 17 + 68?",
      "answers": [
        "87",
        "85",
        "83"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "85",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 59 + 95?",
      "answers": [
        "153",
        "151",
        "154"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "154",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 69 - 2?",
      "answers": [
        "70",
        "65",
        "67"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "67",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2 * 5?",
      "answers": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "9"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 33 + 2?",
      "answers": [
        "38",
        "35",
        "33"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "35",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 + 20?",
      "answers": [
        "25",
        "26",
        "23"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 70 / 10?",
      "answers": [
        "7",
        "10",
        "9"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 37 + 15?",
      "answers": [
        "54",
        "51",
        "52"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "52",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 86 + 75?",
      "answers": [
        "162",
        "160",
        "161"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "161",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 + 75?",
      "answers": [
        "84",
        "87",
        "85"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "85",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 52 + 78?",
      "answers": [
        "131",
        "132",
        "130"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "130",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 12 / 2?",
      "answers": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 54 + 72?",
      "answers": [
        "129",
        "127",
        "126"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "126",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 43 + 57?",
      "answers": [
        "98",
        "99",
        "100"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "100",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 83 - 73?",
      "answers": [
        "10",
        "9",
        "11"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 62 - 23?",
      "answers": [
        "39",
        "42",
        "36"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 87 - 19?",
      "answers": [
        "68",
        "69",
        "66"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "68",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 18 / 9?",
      "answers": [
        "4",
        "3",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 91 + 76?",
      "answers": [
        "168",
        "165",
        "167"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "167",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 25 + 76?",
      "answers": [
        "104",
        "98",
        "101"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "101",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 77 / 7?",
      "answers": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 * 11?",
      "answers": [
        "64",
        "66",
        "67"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4 * 11?",
      "answers": [
        "46",
        "44",
        "47"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 80 / 8?",
      "answers": [
        "10",
        "12",
        "11"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 11 * 12?",
      "answers": [
        "130",
        "135",
        "132"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "132",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 18 + 4?",
      "answers": [
        "22",
        "24",
        "23"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 18 - 15?",
      "answers": [
        "3",
        "5",
        "0"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 42 / 7?",
      "answers": [
        "7",
        "6",
        "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 21 / 7?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "1",
        "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 / 2?",
      "answers": [
        "5",
        "6",
        "4"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 - 12?",
      "answers": [
        "38",
        "33",
        "36"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 83 - 75?",
      "answers": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 60 / 12?",
      "answers": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "7"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 30 - 1?",
      "answers": [
        "31",
        "29",
        "32"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 86 - 72?",
      "answers": [
        "14",
        "15",
        "13"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 22 / 11?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 76 - 69?",
      "answers": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "9"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 98 + 70?",
      "answers": [
        "168",
        "169",
        "167"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "168",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 15 + 93?",
      "answers": [
        "111",
        "108",
        "107"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "108",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 1 * 11?",
      "answers": [
        "8",
        "11",
        "12"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 * 7?",
      "answers": [
        "69",
        "70",
        "67"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "70",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 * 4?",
      "answers": [
        "33",
        "29",
        "32"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 12 / 12?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "0",
        "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 96 / 8?",
      "answers": [
        "9",
        "12",
        "11"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 / 6?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "4"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 86 + 93?",
      "answers": [
        "181",
        "179",
        "182"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "179",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 96 - 19?",
      "answers": [
        "75",
        "79",
        "77"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "77",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 120 / 10?",
      "answers": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "10"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2 * 1?",
      "answers": [
        "4",
        "2",
        "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 12 * 1?",
      "answers": [
        "9",
        "14",
        "12"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 1 * 4?",
      "answers": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 60 - 25?",
      "answers": [
        "33",
        "35",
        "38"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "35",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 32 + 17?",
      "answers": [
        "52",
        "48",
        "49"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 100 - 73?",
      "answers": [
        "28",
        "27",
        "25"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 / 1?",
      "answers": [
        "3",
        "1",
        "0"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 41 + 75?",
      "answers": [
        "116",
        "114",
        "113"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "116",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 84 + 39?",
      "answers": [
        "125",
        "123",
        "122"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "123",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 100 + 39?",
      "answers": [
        "136",
        "139",
        "137"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "139",
      "enabled": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 99 + 74?",
      "answers": [
        "171",
        "173",
        "175"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "173",
      "enabled": 1
    }
  ]
}